<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Hauts' Utility Bionics</name>
    <author>Hautarche</author>
    <packageId>Hautarche.HautsBionics</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<description>Provides many new, powerful bionics with which to enhance and specialize your colonists. Some are simple stat boosts, but others have rare or unique functions, like self-firing ranged attacks, passive skill xp gain, charge-based damage negation, activatable combat abilities, resource generation from ingesting food, and more.

With Royalty: generate psyfocus in new ways, make skipgates at further ranges, and cheapen the cost of Word psycasts.

With Ideology: increase the duration of ideo abilities, strengthen ideo moods and opinions, and produce more dryads from connected gauranlen trees. Some memes have unique augments.

With Biotech: empower bloodfeeders, enhance genetic breath weapons, duplicate genomes, and sacrifice physical health to improve mechanitor stats.

With Anomaly: further modify ghouls, immunize your colonists from metalhorror infection, and upgrade archotech bionics with the insidious power of the void.

Additional bionics will appear if you are also running certain other mods.

To increase the availability of each type of bionic, the mod options let you increase the number of body parts that traders will sell.

See the full descriptions here: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1EZe2Qz7jWTP9hi1ZbJXjx9ABb1gYi2OctJR3SbubEVg/edit?usp=sharing
    </description>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/HautsLogo_Draft0</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Hautarche.HautsFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>Hauts Framework</displayName>
			<!--<steamWorkshopUrl></steamWorkshopUrl>-->
			<downloadUrl>https://drive.google.com/drive/u/2/folders/1NHDZpL4TDIqgiq2ofa1f-1dXN8VUVG5u?fbclid=IwZXh0bgNhZW0CMTEAAR1UzkYW6Fj1VbcShQ0xB6JOt-WUbze81UWVjyXZFtyAqLKEoqVJUCWGqHo_aem_0-eVh1myTUvt2VXpuvK-ZQ</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VPsycastsE</li>
		<li>Hautarche.HautsFramework</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>